adeccowaytowork.com 2017-04-23

# Adecco Way to Work ™ Privacy Statement - Adecco Way to Work™

## Privacy Policy for [www.adeccowaytowork.com](https://www.adeccowaytowork.com/#)

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you about the conditions in which your personal data (as defined in the applicable data protection legislation) is collected and processed on this website ([www.adeccowaytowork.com](http://www.adeccowaytowork.com/)). This website is owned and operated by Adecco Group, A.G. a Swiss company having its registered address at Sägereistrasse, 10 – CH-8152 Glattbrugg – Switzerland (”we” or ”us”).

### Collecting and processing your Personal Data

We will collect your personal data that you provide by filling in the form/s on this website.  We may collect your first and last name, email address, country and city of residence, date of birth, telephone number, level of education, language skills. Also we may ask you about your experience in international environments and availability to travel due to the program CEO for One Month; your interest to work in the future for Adecco and your work preferred areas. Finally how you heard about us.

Fields marked with an asterisk (*) are mandatory to be filled.

We will use your personal data for the following purposes:

  * To make possible your application process and participation in the different programs described in this website (e.g. CEO for One Month, workshops, Experience Work Day or Street Day);
  * To help support your employability;
  * To provide job offers according to your profile;
  * To allow us to contact you and to inform you about our services, opportunities and special events that we believe you will find valuable;
  * To notify you about changes of this website; and
  * To send you information about us, our related companies and possibly about third parties that may be of interest to you.

In order to achieve the above purposes and/or provide you with the best services and/or opportunities, it will be necessary for us to disclose your information to third parties.

However, this disclosure will only occur in the following circumstances:

  * To other companies part of Adecco Group (i.e. direct and indirect subsidiaries of Adecco Group, A.G.) that you can visit at <http://www.adeccogroup.com/worldwide-locations/> which will help you and us to achieve the purposes above;

  * which will help and you and us achieve the purposes above;
  * To our suppliers, customers, contractors and agents: From time to time we may engage or employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf or in order to enforce or apply our terms of website use and other agreements. Examples may include, administrative functions associated with this website or the hosting by a third party. In fact, the website is operated and hosted by VICE Iberia MediaGroup, S.L. with registered address at Calle Alava, 140 – Sobreatico, 08018 Barcelona, Spain and hosted by COLT Technology Services, S.A.U. with registered address at C/ Acero, 5-7 08038 Barcelona, Spain and their respective subcontractors. Both companies shall have access to only that personal data required by it to perform their functions, and these companies may not use such data for any other purposes; and
  * Where required by applicable laws, we will share personal data with government or law enforcement authorities.

Whenever your personal data is transferred within Adecco Group or to third parties, your personal data will be processed in accordance with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

In addition to the rules of this Privacy Policy, further data privacy rules and regulations may apply, which you will find on the websites of the Adecco entity in your home country available here: <http://www.adeccogroup.com/worldwide-locations/>

We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is processed securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### Cookies

We use “cookies” in order to gather information about user behaviour. Cookies are small text files that your web browser places on your computer’s hard drive. They allow us to register anonymous data about user behaviour, for instance, and information about which browser our visitors use. We do not use cookies to gather personal data or other information related to our users.

This information saved by our web servers includes information concerning browsers, operating systems and the IP addresses of computers used to access the site. The IP address can provide information on Internet Service Providers used and Geographical zones. Furthermore, our web servers will register which website our users visited prior to visiting the site as well as the date, time and duration of their visit. At no time is this data attributed to specific users.

Cookies help us to improve the Website and to deliver a better and more personalised service. You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the storing of cookies. This will remove all details from the cookie. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of the Website or use certain functionality. Unless you have adjusted your browser settings so that it will refuse cookies, our systems will issue cookies each time you access the Website. Please note that other website of interest linked here may also use cookies, over which we have no control.

If your computer is shared by other people, we advise that you do not select the “remember my details” option when a Service offers such option to store certain information entered by you.

For further information pertaining to the usage of cookies on the Website please refer to our Cookie Policy, [clicking here](https://www.adeccowaytowork.com/bundles/adeccoawpsite/documents/privacy_policy.pdf).

### Security and Accessibility

We are committed to protecting the security of your personal data. We implement a variety of security technologies and procedures to protect your personal data that we collect on line, against loss, improper use or alteration and from any unauthorized access or disclosure. Systems administration staff is governed by strict confidentiality/non-disclosure agreements and operational procedures.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data when transmitted to this website therefore any transmission is at your own risk.

### Links to other websites

This website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave this website, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable for that website.

### Your rights, questions, comments and contact information

If you have any questions or complaints regarding our statement of privacy practices as related to your specific information, or to request access, modification or deletion to your data, please send an email to [feedback.website@adecco.com](mailto:feedback.website@adecco.com) or contact us by postal mail to:

Adecco Group, A.G.  
Group Communications Department  
Postal address:  
Sägereistrasse,10  
CH- 8152 Glattbrugg  
Switzerland

### Changes to this Privacy Statement

Adecco will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the “last updated” date at the end of this Privacy Policy.

If you do not accept this Policy please leave our website.

Last update: February, 2017
